ELISABETH VICENTE

Front-end Developer

vicente.elisabeth@gmail.com

0751 967 4237

About Me

Over 10 years of experience as a Front-end Developer.

While at **Ted Baker** as Front-end developer, I have been building complex content pages, combining **HTML**, **CSS** (using SASS), and Javascript.

In 2022, the company decided to re-platform and went for a Single Page Application Solution, using **React** and **Next.js**, which gave me the opportunity to familiarise myself with these two technologies.

Following the launch, as part of CICD, I developed several features, such as check instore availability, mini basket popup, sticky add to bag option on mobile, and also owned bug tickets.

In November 2023, the new management team decided to modernise the existing digital solution and started the migration process to **Contentful**. From the early stage of the project, I participated in the decision-making process, writing technical tickets in **Jira** for new features and improved existing ones. I was also part of the **end-to-end user testing** phase.

I developed a deep understanding of Contentful, being in charge of its configuration (creation of **content models** and content) and the training of the content team.

While working at Chorus, a web agency based in Paris specialised in portal websites, I was the sole person in charge of the Front-end development aspect for complex structures, combining HTML, CSS and Javascript.

Involved throughout the whole creation process, I have worked closely with both the web design and back-end team. I was in charge of building the best UX possible, preventing any subsequent technical issues that could emerge from faulty design and developing the best responsive interface.

Education

2010

Bachelor Web Developer

Hetic (former Cifacom) • Montreuil, Paris France

2002

BTS Office Manager

Sylvia Montfort Institute • Chartres, France

Spoken Languages

201 Saint John Street

Stirling Court, Flat 28

EC1V 4LZ LONDON

Work Experience

August 2018 - August 2024

Front-end Developer • Ted Baker • London, UK

October 2023 - Replatform & Migration to Contentful

React Next.js Javascript HTML5 SASS Contentful

End-to-End User Testing Jira Tickets

• March 2022: Migration to a Single Page Application & CICD

React Styled Components Jest Material UI Next.js Javascript

HTML5 SASS Bloomreach BRXM

BAU 2018-Present

Content Pages and Promotions Campaigns Development

Javascript HTML5 SASS Bloomreach BRXM Hybris

AB Testing

Optimizely Webtrends

July 2015 - July 2018

Maternity Leave

July 2011 - June 2015

Front-end Developer • Chorus • Paris, France

• cbnews.fr • citizenkid.com • jeuxvideomagazine.com

HTML5 CSS jQuery Library Javascript codelgniter

Responsive Website Newsletter

madeinpotager.com

HTML5 CSS jQuery Library Javascript Symphony

Responsive Website

klepierre.fr

HTML5 CSS jQuery Library Javascript EzPublish

Responsive Website Newsletter

Side Project

amboora.com

HTML5 CSS Liquid Templating Javascript Shopify

BEGINNER

Skills

Programming-Languages React

Javascript CSS - SASS HTML

CMS

Bloomreach BRXM

Contentful Shopify

Softwares

Jira

Git Photoshop •

EXPERT